it turns out that your government is bombing you The
это ваша власть бомбит вас получается
drone is flying look they give the drone coordinates
Дрон летит смотри дрону дают координаты
Yes, a military object, everything is flying if
Да военного объекта всё он летит если бы
your government had not
ваша власть не не
deviated, they would have shot down the wing badly
отклонялись подбили крыло бы плохо сбили
Yes, and it turns out that he turned away and
Да и он получается оп отвернулся и
flew at the
полетел на
houses Hello, what city are you from,
дома Привет Ты из какого
what city in Russia are you from  I
города из какого города России ты
live not far from Moscow
недалеко от Москвы живу
specifically Moscow region Okay
конкретно Московская область Хорошо
I got it you are some kind of Streamer No and what are you
понял ты какой-то Стример Нет а что ту
doing T roulette I communicate with people Let's
делаешь Т рулетке общаюсь с людьми Давай
chat Me and the person it seems we can
пообщаемся Я и человек вроде то можно
chat Streamer no
пообщаться Стример нет
Okay what do you want to know You are 18 yes
Хорошо что хотите знать Тебе 18 есть
yes I understand Who are you studying to be a
есть понял На кого учишься
veterinarian
ветеринара
veterinarian A  why
ветеринар А почему именно эту профессию
did I want this profession I wanted to be a doctor but I
захотела я хотела быть врачом но не
couldn't choose a direction let's say so
могла выбрать направление скажем так вот
and I am actually involved in equestrian sports
и я занимаюсь собственно конным спортом
and my trainer is like Why do
и у меня тренер такая типа А почему тебе
n't you become a veterinarian like she's also a doctor
не пойти на ветеринара типа тоже же врач
Well I thought She agreed
Ну я подумала Она согласилась вот так
so now I'm studying  to the vet
что сейчас Учусь на ветеринара
how old am I yes And how old do I look they
сколько мне лет да А насколько я выгляжу
say a man is how old he
говорят мужчине столько насколько он
looks I don't know well try to
выглядит Я не знаю ну попробуйте
guess Okay you don't look very
угадать Ладно выглядите не сильно
grown up let
взрослым
's say No not 20  29 let it be I don't care
допустим Нет не 20 29 пусть будет пофиг
Almost guessed sl
Почти угадала сль
43 not bad
43 неплохо
Well not twice in one and a half somewhere Well
Ну не в два раза в полторашку где-то Ну
Okay let it be And how much are you Let me
Хорошо пусть будет А тебе сколько Давай
guess now
угадаю
like this
так
21 19
21 19
me I just thought Damn well maybe no maybe not
меня Я просто думал Блин ну может нет
so
может не так
little so little I think since I study  that means
мало так мало думаю раз учится то значит
somewhere between 18 and 22 decided 21
где-то ещ от 18 до 22 решил 21
how do you feel about the fact that
как относишся к тому что сейчас воюют
our
наши
countries are fighting now What kind of politics have we gone through Ugh I don't like
страны Что за политика пошла Фу не люблю
this not this is just that we are just
такое не это просто просто вот мы как
ordinary people I don't influence the war you don't
простые люди я Не влияю на войну ты не
influence we can't do anything  change But
влияешь мы ничего не можем изменить Но
we can talk about it simply
мы можем поговорить об этом просто как
how we live, how we perceive it,
вот нам живётся как мы воспринимаем это
how do you think? Why are our countries fighting?
как ты считаешь Почему воюет наши
BN, what can I say? I
БН что могу сказать
like it and because
нравится и по причине того что там якобы
people are supposedly dying there? I don’t know how
люди гибнут Я уж не знаю насколько Всё
true all this is. Just, well, ice can be there
это правда Просто ну ледь там могут всё
anything you want Well, of course, of course, it's
что угодно вот и Ну конечно же конечно
uncomfortable that with countries,
некомфортно что со странами вот эти вот
all these sanctions and everything else, it's really
все санкции и всё остальное это прям
very uncomfortable And what exactly makes you
очень некомфортно А чем вам именно
uncomfortable with the sanctions
некомфортно санкцией
Well, at the very least  because I'm
Ну как минимум из-за того что я ну как
like a rider, I do equestrian sports,
бы всадник я конным спортом занимаюсь
this is the bare minimum,
это самое минимальное на что
it's even trivial to order something from
это даже банально заказать что-то из
another country, here in Russia it's not
другой страны у нас в России это не
as developed as, for example, in
настолько развито как например в той же
Germany,
Германии
and let's say they have something there  -or to buy it
и допустим у них там что-либо купить
will cost one amount from us on the price
будет стоить одну сумму у нас на ценко
at least
как минимум раза в
twice this is just the minimum plus to everything there
два это вот прям минимум плюс ко всему
are certain difficulties so that
определённые трудности имеются с тем
simply
чтобы просто напросто
in Well, you can say so, it
в Ну можно и так сказать просто как
was simply at least much easier to order all this,
минимум было легче намного это всё
that is, relatively speaking  now it's
заказать то есть условно говоря сейчас
not even the fact that the border is closed
даже Дело не в том что граница закрыта
That is, all this can be bypassed but simply
То есть это всё можно обойти но просто
those groups that can order us,
те группы которые могут заказать наму
roughly speaking Well, resellers In short, they
грубо говоря Ну перекупы Короче они
understandably inflate the price for themselves in their pockets
понятное дело завышают це себе в карман
So,
Вот
and what
и А чем
or you are still on parental
или ты пока ещё на родительском
support I am some kind of  at that time I worked
обеспечении я какое-то время я работала
at the stable as a trainer and groom there everything
на конюшне как тренер коновод там всё
was together at the moment I am just
вместе было на данный момент я только
studying because I have no time for anything else
учусь поскольку времени на остальное
at all, that is, I have my own horse and
вообще нету то есть У меня своя лошадь и
I need to at least allocate time for it
мне как минимум на неё надо Выделить
plus get to school So Well,
время плюс до учёбы доехать Так что Ну у
I can't  it doesn't work out that your horse is yours.
меня никак не получается что свое лошадь
That's what I mean  does it belong to you
Это в смысле она тебе принадлежит ты её
did you buy it or are you just assigned to it
купила или ты просто за ней закреплена
as the one who looks after it No It's ours,
как тот кто присматривать Нет Прямо своя
that is, the horse we bought And what do your
то есть купленная нами лошадь А у вас
parents do? Mom doesn't work.
родители кем работают мама не работает
Dad is the deputy director of a
папа зам директор
company there for landscaping, in short, Moscow in
фирмы там по озеленению короче Москвы в
what area? Landscaping of Moscow - that's me
какой сфере озеленение Москвы - это я не
I don't know how to explain it to you correctly. I
знаю как как вам правильно объяснить А я
myself don't really get into it, it's just that basically the
сама не особо вникаю просто в основном
work is on, let's say, when they
работы по скажем так вот дорогу когда
lay a road. I think they have
прокладывают по-моему с дорогами у них
everything connected with roads, too, but I do
тоже всё это связано но на счёт этого я
n't know for sure about that. They supply tree seedlings,
точно не знаю а они саженцы деревьев
like, there.  yes grass
поставляют типа там да траву Вот эту вот
Sow this along the road there for example near the
засеять вдоль дороги там например у
metro make these steam everything everything I
метро сделать вот эти пар всё всё понял
understood I understood yes I understood Well this is a pretty
Понял да понял понял Ну это довольно
promising thing yes it can provide the
перспективная вещь да может обеспечить
daughter with a personal horse So yes well and
дочери личного коня Так что да нука а
what kind of horse do you have
какой у вас
I have an English thoroughbred
конь у меня английская чистокровная
this is what color  what a redhead redhead do you like
это а расцветка какая рыжий рыжий любите
redheads specifically
рыжего именно
Yes, it's generally a very
Да это вообще там очень там очень
long situation there as Well, not that it's
длинная ситуация как Ну не то чтобы она
long,
длинная
just let's say that not everything worked out the way
просто скажем так не всё сложилось так
I would like I really like the
как я бы хотела мне очень нравится
Kinsky breed of horses maybe you've heard I don't
порода кински лошадей может слышали Не
know
знаю
in principle They are somehow  similar to the
вот в принципе Они чем-то схожи с
thoroughbred Lo That is, if we take
чистокровного Ло То есть если брать
the Anzei, then this is the maximum, let's say,
анцев то это максимально скажем так
horses they were taken out for racing
лошади они были для вывезены для скачек
in the desert there, that is, these are still
в пустыне там то есть это всё-таки
hot horses that Well, they are
горячие лошади которые Ну таки Они
really very light in structure and
реально очень лёгкие По строению и
it turned out that I wanted exactly this for a very long time
получилось так что я очень долго хотела
this horse but was trained on
именно эту лошадь но занималась на
Karachayev this is a completely different
Карачаев это вообще абсолютно другая
horse because well this was the
лошадь потому что ну это была
only opportunity to jump I am a
единственная возможность прыгать я
show jumper
конкуристы
and there are different disciplines there is show
да там разные дисциплины есть конкуре
jumping and it turned out that we
занимаюсь и получилось так что мы
had a fight with the owner of the previous stable
поругались с хозяйкой конюшни предыдущей
and had to go to the one where we are
и пришлось ехать на ту на которой мы на
currently standing
данный момент стоим
and purely by chance passing by the stall we
и чисто случайно проходя мимо денника мы
saw this horse actually his
увидели этого коня собственно его фш
name is fsh and decided to buy it all of course it
зовут и решили купить это всё конечно
took a long time but it was just by chance we passed by and
долго было но так случайно проходили о
decided to buy the horse Well I said it
решили коня купить Ну я я и сказала это
wasn't just a click let's say so but
было не просто по щелчку скажем так но
there's just nothing more to tell
там просто особо рассказывать больше
that is, I was just wondering
нечего то есть мне просто было интересно
I've never bought horses I'm wondering
я никогда не покупал коней Мне интересно
how people buy horses now that is, I
как люди сейчас покупают коней то есть
was walking near the stall Oh, the horse is cool
так шёл возле денника О Конь прикольный
Let's decide not really, I'm
Давайте реши не на самом деле вот очень
usually very lucky  this is not really happening it
повезло обычно это всё не так происходит
just happened that for
реально просто получилось так что я на
about six months I was
протяжение наверное полугода я родителей
trying to persuade my parents to buy a horse because
настраивала на покупку лошади потому что
well it was necessary let's say our horse
ну необходимо было скажем так у нас конь
was injured Besides at that time
травмировался К тому же на тот момент
I
вот я так
understand there was a horse there sorry about the price That's
понимаю там конь сори с ценой Так скорее
most likely  No, not always, not always Well,
всего Нет не всегда вообще не всегда Ну
ours at the time of purchase cost
вот наш на момент покупки стоил
350 350 what Rubles thousand rubles that
350 350 чего Рублей тысяч руб это
comes out to 3,500
получается 3.500
dollars Well, at the moment somewhere yes And I
долларов ну на данный момент где-то да А
understood that it is cheap Well, like an
понял то это это дешёвый Ну типа
inexpensive taco but in fact I was very
недорогой тако а на самом деле очень
lucky with the horse because  that he was
повезло с лошадью потому что он был
exactly promising, it turns out they
именно перспективный его получается
took him away from the stud farm, he participated in the races,
забрали с конного завода он в скачках
but look, do you have, for example,
участвовал а смотрите А у Вас например
only girls or are there guys
только девчонки или парни тоже там есть
at these races? No, guys also
на этих скачках Нет парни тоже
take up what-what I don’t participate in the races,
занимают что-что я не в скачках участвую
the race is this, when the competitions Well
скачке это вот сто когда соревнования Ну
in all these horse matters I just
вот в этих всяких конных делах Я просто
wanted to ask, are there guys
хотел спросить а есть такие парни
who were taken to war from your horse
которых забрали на войну из ваших конных
parties? Yes, they were taken from someone I No, well, I
тусовок Да у кого-то забрали я я Не ну я
don’t know exactly, I didn’t ask, but I heard
не знаю точно я не уточняла но я слышала
that  someone Yes they took them there no yes it's not
что у кого-то Да забирали там нет да не
like that we have a woman who
так получается у нас у женщины которая
was involved in equestrian sports her husband
занималась конным спортом у неё мужа
was taken away just for the war he was
забрали вот как раз на войну он
alive and alive I don't know really in my opinion
живой а живой не знаю правда по-моему
Yes regarding athletes I understand that
Да насчёт спортсменов Я так понимаю что
no because that's exactly all  those who
нет потому что именно все те которые на
were on everyone's lips and they are on everyone's lips they
слуху были и они они есть на слуху они
travel they perform calmly that is
ездят они спокойно выступают то есть они
they are rich kids no one will take them there yes yes it is
они мажоры их никто не возьмёт там да
quite possible I don't know that's it for the
пра вполне возможно не знаю вот Это для
type of SPO Yes as I
вид СПО Да я так
understand it investments Yes it requires a lot
понимаю вложений Да очень много требует
that is very difficult  to fall precisely to a
то есть очень сложно выпасть именно на
professional level if with
профессиональный уровень если с
finances limited let's say
финансами ограничено скажем
so I understand that there is not only In
так я так понимаю что там не только В
finances there probably also
финансах там ещё наверно влияние
should be the influence of parents because there I
родителей должно быть потому что там я
understand judges these coaches all
так понимаю судьи эти тренера это всё
that in fact enough VS honestly yy
то на самом деле достаточно ВС честно йй
extent in our
мере в нашем
we are not particularly behind, that is, well, the Armed Forces are so
у нас особо не зади то есть ну там ВС
visible there that well, how would you just try to
видно настолько что ну как бы тут попроб
sue here? And so, in general, the financial
только засудить А так вообще финансово
impact is that it is not
влияет то что связи не
particularly easy to develop connections, it
особо просто раскрутиться попроще можно
will be easier, and there is someone among my acquaintances who has
будет а есть среди знакомых кто-то кто
already died in
погиб уже на
the war. Now, for
войне Сейчас
a second, I  I heard it at our stables Yes,
секунду я слышала у нас на конюшне Да
someone talked about it Well, so that you
кто-то говорил об этом Ну так чтоб вы
know some people, your relatives
знали каких-то людей Ваших родственников
Personally, I don’t have such a large circle of
Лично у меня не настолько большой круг
friends who are much
общения кто сильно
older and well, older than my wounds Well, let’s
переваливает и ну старше моих ра ну
say, not the dead but the wounded Yes, there
скажем не погибших а раненых Да раненые
were wounded And who  you have a wounded friend from
были А кто раненый у вас из знакомых у
our dad's
нас по папиной
side, it turns out he's dad's brother.
линии там получается брат папиной Вот у
He just happened to get slightly injured in the war.
него как раз он на войне чуть-чуть
Well, it wasn't just slightly.
поранился Ну там не то чтобы чуть-чуть
I didn't understand what actually happened,
Я не поняла что произошло на самом деле
but he injured his arm. And what  happened
но там руку он повредил А что произошло
there slipped fell or There is a bullet or
там подскользнулся упал или Там пуля или
Drone bullet bullet
Дрон пуля пуля
understood dad's this relative went to war
понял папин этот родственник на войну
called up understood Well it was not of their own
призвали понял Ну это не по своему
free will
желанию было
Here are people in Ukraine but not of their own
Вот людей в Украине но не по своему
free will yes yes and yes there is a friend of ours in the
желанию да да а е есть знакомый у нас в
regiment he lives precisely because  I think
полке жит он именно по по-моему по
he went there on his own accord to
своему желанию он поехал периодически
come periodically with news, let's say, but
вот приезжать с новостями скажем так но
what kind of news does he bring?
какие какие новости он привозит
He and dad mostly talk, I
м Они с папой в основном разговаривают я
don't get into it, but in
вот не вникаю вот а так
general he's somewhere, let's say  so he's somewhere in the rear
вообще он он где-то скажем так он в тылу
That is, he's like that he's fine And how do
где-то То есть он так он нормально А как
you feel about the fact that people are dying in
ты относишься к тому что умирает люди в
Ukraine Because when you said at the beginning
Украине Потому что ты когда в начале
Well, and supposedly they're dying there I mean supposedly they're
говорила Ну и там якобы умирают В смысле
dying I meant exactly that
якобы умирают имела в виду именно то что
we too when I  I was sitting in this app
мы тоже я когда сидела в этом приложении
talking to a guy I think from Ukraine It
общалась с парнем по-моему с Украины Это
was a young boy I think We have
был по-моему молодой мальчик У нас
one piece of information you have different
информация одна у вас собственно другая
information What information do
и Какая информация информация у всех
you all have the same information at that time it was a dispute
одна вы на тот момент это было был спор
about who started it first so here
именно в том кто первый начал так тут
Russia there is no dispute here Everything is clear here
Россия тут спора нет Тут всё понятно
Russia started it But that's all And
Россия же начала Но это вот и всё Вот и
here is the answer to the question we have information
вот вам ответ на вопрос у нас информация
that our border
что на нашу границу нашу границу
was crossed
пересекла
because of this, that's why there was talk about the
изза это началось поэтому и шла речь о
fact that the information is unreliable everywhere and
том что информация везде недостоверная и
most likely in terms of quantity  killed people
скорее всего по количеству убитых людей
too most likely Well look You see
тоже скорее всего Ну смотри Ты же видишь
that Russia destroyed Mariupol
что Россия уничтожила Мариуполь
destroyed Bakhmut you see These
уничтожила бахмут ты же видишь Эти
photos you have the Internet since you
фотографии у тебя есть Интернет раз ты
are communicating with me now yes You have the
со мной общаешься сейчас да У тебя есть
Internet You definitely saw the destroyed
Интернет Ты по-любому видела разрушенные
cities arrivals Yes you saw from Russian missiles
города прилёты Да от российских ракет
Ukraine  And in order not to give the opportunity on
в Украине А дабы не дать возможность на
our territory, let's say, we are
нашей территории скажем так у нас же
now talking about the fact that in
сейчас речь о том что
Donetsk, in my opinion, I
а Донецк по-моему Я
apologize. Now, in my opinion, military actions are being conducted there.
извиняюсь Сейчас по-моему там ведутся
And the point is that if
боевые действия И речь о том что если не
we do not move, let's say, in your
мы будем двигать скажем так в вашу
direction, the line of our  touches let's say
сторону линию сво прикосновения скажем
so then it will move in our
так то это будет двигаться в нашу
direction here when u have cash on Donetsk
сторону вот при у есть нали на Донец
captured this is Ukraine and where should
захватили это же есть Украина а докуда
you move this to Lvov to
вы эту нию должны двигать до Львова до
Washington I don't know but the talk is also about the
Вашингтона Я не знаю но речь Ещё идёт о
fact that the US is getting
том что вот у США получается ещё
some other-  then the countries of Dani, in my opinion, if I'm not
какие-то страны Дани по-моему Если не
mistaken, supply weapons to Ukraine
ошибаюсь поставляет оружие Украине не
not so
Украине поставляет оружие не для того
that they can defend themselves, but so that there will be attacks on the territory, they attacked Ukraine once. Ukraine is supplied weapons not so that it can defend itself, but so that
чтобы она защищалась а для того чтобы
it can attack, so Ukraine  already so Ukraine
она нападала так Украина уже так Украина
by definition is defending itself because you are
по определению защищается потому что вы
the aggressor for example look if
агрессор например смотри если
Ukraine hits Moscow with a drone it is
Украина бьёт беспилотником по Москве это
not Ukraine attacking it is
Украина не нападает Это она
defending itself Okay good then in your
защищается Окей хорошо тогда по вашему
opinion Why hit populated areas
мнению Зачем бить по населённым пунктам
and not those  places for example
а не по тем местам например
Where there is
Где содержится допустим так скажем
some kind of weapon or transport that
какое-то оружие либо транспорт который
can
может вам
harm you Ukraine is not Ukraine just
навредить Украина не Украина как раз
strikes only military facilities or
бьёт только по военным объектам или по
transport yes And where where it struck
транспорту да А где где ударила
literally in
буквально вот в
Podolsk not far from us it was a
Подольске совсем недалеко от нас это был
populated area several
населённый пункт прилетело несколько
drones flew in  Where exactly Where Where did it fly to
Дронов Куда именно Куда Куда прилетело
what
какой
object do you have there Chemical plant in Podolsk
объек там у вас там Химзавод в Подольске
No, exactly to a populated area to houses Do you
Да нет именно в населённый пу в дома А
know why it flew to houses
знаешь почему в дома прилетела потому
because look, a Ukrainian drone is flying to
что смотри э украинский Дрон летит на
your plant or to a military unit, and a
ваш завод или на воинскую часть а
Russian one, instead of shooting it down Yes
русский вместо того чтобы его сбить Да
they start jamming the radio signal and because of
начинают глушить радиосигнал и он из-за
this it gets confused and deviates a little
этого сбивается и немножко отклоняется
if your government had jammed it a
если бы ваша власть сбивала его ещё
long time ago why did it let it fly to
давно почему она дала ему долететь до
Podolsk It could have jammed it under the
Подольска Она же могла его сбить ещё под
border though But it lets it
границей правда А так она даёт чтобы
fly to Podolsk they turn on
долетел до Подольска включают
electronic interference so that it  got lost
радиоэлектронные помехи чтобы он сбился
and it ends up somewhere wrong it's your
и он попадает куда-то не туда это ваша
government bombing you it turns out the drone is flying
власть бомбит вас получается Дрон летит
look they give the drone  coordinates Yes military
смотри дрону дают координаты Да военного
object everything it flies if your government did
объекта всё он летит если бы ваша власть
not deviate
не отклонялись
case if take and here is the
случай если брать а вот это вот
supplied weapon information that they
поставляемое оружие информацию которую
give that there are huge quantities and
дают что там огромные количество и
drones and military aircraft
беспилотники и самолёты военного именно
and weapons where it all
назначения и оружие куда это всё
goes down in that case everything goes down
спускается в таком случае спускается всё
yes Well look  already according to data more than
да Ну смотри уже по данным более более
700,000 dead Russians That's where
700.000 погибших россиян Вот это туда
all these weapons went down
спускалась всё это оружие
yeah Yeah And what's so then I don't even know
да Угу А что так тогда я не знаю даже
how to comment now
както сейчас от
Well that's their business In fact Well I
Ну это их дела На самом деле Ну я
understand that this is actually good
понимаю что это хорошего на самом деле
that is well wait yeah  But it turns out
то есть ну подожди да Но получается
look how easy it is to stop the war
смотри как очень просто остановить войну
Russia withdraws its troops from Ukraine
Россия выводит свои войска из Украины
there from Crimea Donetsk Lugansk and that's it and
там с Крыма Донецка Луганска и всё и
stops the very next day the
останавливается на следующий же день
war stops
останавливается война
territorial claims to Russia that
претензии территориальных к России что
we need to take Krasnodar There and so
нам нужно забрать Краснодар Там и так
on yes that is we take ours Yes
дальше да то есть мы забираем своё Да
only  there Donetsk Lugansk Crimea Kursk
только там Донецк Луганск Крым Курск
like and that's all we don't need someone else's Why do
типа и всё нам чужого не надо Почему
you think that Crimea is yours because it has
считаете что Крым ваш потому что он он
always been there since the time of Kievan
всегда был изначально со времен Киевской
Rus it wasn't always transferred in my opinion
Руси не всегда его передали по-моему
no no  no during the Kievan Rus he
нетт нет нет во время Киевской Руси он
was our Kievan there
был наш Киевский там тмутараканское
was the Tmutarakan principality in
княжество было
the world ru prince Yes he was baptized in Crimea
вми ре ру князь Да он в Крыму принимал
this is our Crimea was originally yours
Крещение это наш Крым изначально был вам
Lenin illegally handed it over then crunch He
Ленин его не законно передал потом хрум
gave it back to us and
Нам его назад отдал и
that's it Lenin Lenin came up with the Russian
всё Ленин Ленин придумал Российскую
Federation well you  you see before the revolution there
Федерацию ну ты ж понимаешь до революции
was no Russian Federation you know
не было Российской Федерации зна это ж
Lenin invented the Russian
Ленин придумал Российскую
Federation took the capital from Petrograd
Федерацию взял столицу из петрограда
moved to Moscow
перес в Москву
Well if you get the document now It
Ну если документ сейчас доставать Он же
remained with us in any case that is
в любом случае оставался у нас то есть
not How exactly according to the documents in the UN
не Как как раз по документам в ООН
look in the UN internationally everything is there  all
смотри в ООН международно там все все
agreements when made between states are
договора когда между государствами
registered in the UN Yes,
делаются они регистрируются в ООН Да вот
Prince Vladimir Yes, when he received
князь Владимир Да когда получил в
Crimea as a gift from the Polovtsian prince
дарственную Крым от половецкого князя Да
Yes, this agreement was registered in the UN
есть этот договор зарегистрировали в ООН
Yes, Bohdan Khmelnitsky, when he established
Да Богдан Хмельницкий когда установил
sovereignty over Crimea,
суверенитет над Крымом договор
registered the agreement in he registered all agreements over the
зарегистрировал в он все договора за
last thousand years on ownership
последние тысяч лет о принадлежности
Ukraine Crimea Ukraine registered in the
Украине Крыма Украине зарегистрированы в
UN Well, I conditionally speaking now e if you
ООН Ну я условно говоря сейчас е если же
type in the information in any browser you
вбить в информацию в любом браузере вы
even that Crimea  No no I typed in I
даже что Крым Нет нет я вбивал я
checked it doesn't give out
проверял не выдаёт
whose
это чей
Crimea is it
Крым
now with what can't answer on the
сечас с что не может ответить в
Internet there are many with information on this
интернете есть мно с информацией на эту
topic here is what was found in the search Even louder
тему вот что нашлось в поиске Ещё громче
louder Crimea was Scythian Greek
громче Крым был скифский греческим
Gothic Khazar Russian Byzantine
готский хазарским русским византийским
Horde Kim Russian German
ордынским Ким русским германским
Soviet and even some  time
советским и даже некоторое время
Ukrainian in the 15th century the Crimean Khanate
украинским в XV веке Крымское ханство
was In short this story I stop
было Короче эта история останавливаю
Alice she will tell for a long time
Алису она будет долго рассказывать
Why ROSI attacked Ukraine and she will be afraid to
Поче РОСИ нала на Укра и она побоится
answer look for the sake of interest Make it
ответить посмотри ради интереса Сделай
louder Why Russia attacked Ukraine and
громче Почему Россия напала на Украину и
make it louder
громче сделай
Yes I can't hear it there are just a lot of sites with
Да я не слышу просто есть много сайтов с
information on  this topic here is what was found
информацией на эту тему вот что нашлось
in the Yandex search
в поиске Яндекса
Forbs February 24, 2022 Russian President
Forbs 24 февраля 2022 года президент
Vladimir special military operation the
владими специальной военной операции
goals of Russia were declared
целями России были заявлены
demilitarization and denazification of Ukraine
демилитаризация и денацификация Украины
to protect Russia from the
для защиты России от создаваемой западом
military threat created by the West NATO Lenta.ru special
НАТО военной угрозы Lenta.ru специальной
military this look I'm stopping She
военно это смотри останавливаю Она
reads you a Russian site  She reads the
читает тебе русский сайт Она читает
Russian site, I told you about it right away,
русский сайт вот я тебе я сразу об этом
she reads yours, that is, you understand, she
говорила она ваши то есть понимаешь она
reads your Russian sites. And you, I
Ваши русские сайты читает А ты онов с я
told you about it in advance, that we have a pause,
об этом заранее говорила что у нас пауза
that we have information, that is,
что у нас информация
British information in
адо информацию британскую на английском
English, which is registered in it. Well,
языке которая в он зарегистрирована Ну
that is, in he yes I am just a lawyer by
то есть в он да Вот я просто юрист по
education, an international lawyer Yes in he
образованию юрист международник Да в он
has all the treaties Yes all the treaties on
есть все договоры Да все договоры о
Crimea Lenin illegally transferred Crimea to the
Крыме Ленин незаконно был передал Крым
Russian Federation and then Khrushchev, upon
Российской Федерации да потом Хрущёв по
demand, he transferred it back to Ukraine All
требованию он назад передал Украине Всё
these treaties have existed since the time of Prince
эти договоры есть со времён князя
Vladimir he was
Владимира он
registered  all these
регистрировались все эти
as they are agreement And by the way did you
как они договор А ты кстати историю
like history in school we
любила в школе у нас в колледже отличный
had an excellent history teacher in college and she also, I
преподаватель истории был и тоже она
think, by education either a lawyer
по-моему по образованию то ли юрист то
or something Something in this area And
ли Вот что-то вот в этой Вот области а
when Crimea became part of
когда Крым попал в
Russia Why  dates Well,
Россию Почему по датам Ну
I need to open it approximately. I need to
приблизительно мне открыть Надо
look. Well, not just approximately.
посмотреть Ну не просто приблизительно
What century is interesting to me.
Какой век мне интересно
I don’t know the truth. That is, I
Я не знаю правду То есть з есть я не
can’t tell you. Okay, let me give you a
смогу подсказать Хорошо давай так
hint. Uh, the end of the 20th century or the beginning of the 20th
подсказку ээ конец де века или начало XX
century. Most likely, the end of the 20th century. The end of the 20th century. That’s
века скорее всего конец дего конец X
right.
правильно
Yes,
Да
1890, what
1890 какой
year?  no no  no, that's not what we were talking about
год нене не у нас не об этом речь шла
then we were discussing something else a little bit.
тогда мы другое разбирали немножко
That's why 187,
Поэтому 187
3 years before the century,
за 3 года до века
Crimea was given to Lenin yes. And by the way,
Крым был подарен ленином да А кстати
why did Lenin kill
почему Ленин убил
the Tsar? Let's say that I have good stories,
царя Давайте Так я с историй хорошо
things were going well, which Well, let's say
именно дела шли которые Ну скажем так у
we had a certain plan. She  she
нас был план определённый она нам
gave us information we were responsible therefore for
информацию давала мы отвечали поэтому за
the period that she managed to give I
тот промежуток который она успела дать Я
more or less understand but I am not one of those
более-менее разбираюсь но Я не из тех
guys that we have Well
ребят которые вот у нас есть Ну
classmates in fact who
Одногруппники на самом деле которые
really know history very well my
прямо очень хорошо знают историю у меня
level is purely that information
уровень вот чисто вот ту информацию
that she  I know because
которую она дала я знаю потому что она
she told it in a really interesting way. She
реально интересно рассказывала Она
gave the information completely. It was Well, it was
давала информацию полностью это было Ну
really useful, namely,
реально полезно а именно вот разбираться
I haven't tried to figure it out myself.
самой в этом я не
And what do you know about
пробовала А что ты знаешь о
Bandera? Nothing about Lyuri.
бандери ничего а люри
And why did Gorbachev poison
а почему Горбачёв отравил
Lenin? I can only tell you about this provisional
Ленина Я могу только про это временное
government.  Come on, tell me
правительство рассказать Давай расскажи
about the Provisional Government Yes,
про Временное правительство Да кенский
I'm interested in the Kensky one too Let's say
мне тоже интересен Давай у нас скажем
this right now for a second, literally I'll take
так сейчас секунду вот буквально мне
a minute to think
минутку подумать
well Well, that is, you see Yes,
хорошо Ну то есть вы видите Да у меня
I don't have any TV or anything, what am I talking about  remember let's
никаких ТВ ничего нету я про что вспом
say
скажем так
after the revolution if I'm not
после революции если я не
mistaken it wasn't that is the government
ошибаюсь было не то есть правительство
was overthrown there Peter
получается было свергнуто там Пётр
I think was some kind of if I'm not mistaken
по-моему был какой-то если я не ошибаюсь
but it turns out he was overthrown and there
а его получается свергли и на место
was no one to take the place of the government and they decided
правительства не было никого и решили
that instead of the ruler as they called him
что вместо правителя так как звали
the emperor whose drill the Provisional
императора которого сверло Временное
Government also said as in my opinion
правительство тоже сказала как по-моему
Peter I don't remember as in my opinion Peter I don't
Пётр я не помню как по-моему Пётр я не
remember No no no
помню Нет не нет
Bona No no no He is exactly who not he not
Бона Нет нет не Он точно кто не он не
Bonaparte not without without Alice not
Бонапарт же не без без Алисы не не
Bonaparte Bonaparte is Napoleon I  I know
Бонапарт Бонапарт - это Наполеон Я знаю
Well, it just
Ну просто это вот это сейчас очень
sounded very strange now, so I am this
странно звучало поэтому я это
Bona banana banana no no he is a banana yes
Бона банан банан не не он же банан да
after after Nicholas II Yes, his nephew
после после Николая II Да его племянник
banana took the throne and the Provisional
банан зал на престол и Временное
Government rebelled and overthrew
правительство взбунтовалась и скинуло
him, perhaps Yes, I
его возможно Да
know what happened with the Provisional Government, let's
знаю что там с временным правительством
say  so this is the provisional
было скажем так это временное
government
правительство
byst l and a member of the provisional government
быст л и члену временного правительства
there in my opinion if I'm not mistaken Toli
там по-моему если я не ошибаюсь Толи
executed in short everyone died there not Why did
казнили короче там все умерли не Почему
Kerensky dress up as a woman and
Керенский переоделся в женщину и
run away  well basically everything with him and
убежал ну в основном то всё у него с
Lenin was 1:1 first Lenin
Лениным 1:1 было сначала Ленин от
ran away from Kerensky so he could dress up as a
Керенского убежал чтобы переоделся в
woman and run away from the city and then
женщину и убежал из города а потом
Kerensky did the same Finn did it with them
Керенский такой же Фин сделал у них это
Well it's cool in short he couldn't take it her brain is
Ну прикольно короче не выдержал её мозг
easier to feed a horse than to
коня кормить проще чем
think it's a pity she snapped  I warm her up
думать жалко сорвалась я её прогрева
warm up at first with abstract themes Yes
прогрева вначале абстрактными темами Да
because she
потому что она
see her if immediately about politics Yes she
видите её если сразу о политике Да она
would break loose quickly yes And so e Oh there's
бы сорвалась быстро да А так е Ой там
a horse yes yes what she chuh-chuh-chuh
лошадь да да что она чух-чух-чух
relaxes and then you introduce her into
расслабляется а дальше её уже вводишь в
politics subscribe to my Telegram  right
политику подпишись на мий Telegram прям
now wasp and
зараз ос а
pok this is very and very important YouTube is busy
пок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
with us through scarg or in your ban and very
нас через скарг ор в твый бан и дуже
many videos I do not show to people at times I do not
багато вдео не показую людям вчасно не
show information about streams That is why in order for
показуе информация про стрими Тому для
us Mali operational links
того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
are written right now and while there is a video in telegram
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
OKM  and
окм видео
so on  useful information and
теж ва и корисна информация и пон
understand the constant operational connection
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that will show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава Украине
signature N
пидпись N